https://millcraftideas.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Millcraft Investments
AboutHistoryMission & VisionAwards & RecognitionsMeet Our TeamCareersServicesDevelopmentCommercial LeasingResidential LeasingResidential BrokerageProperty ManagementInterior DesignHotel DivisionAboutDevelopmentManagementHotel PortfolioRestaurant PortfolioProjectsProjects
ProjectsTower Two-SixtyEsplanade350 Oliver & LumiereHilton Garden Inn Pittsburgh DowntownRevel + RoostHilton Garden Inn Beaver ValleyHome2 Suites Pittsburgh Area Beaver ValleyHampton Inn North Huntingdon-IrwinMicrotel Inn & Suites by Wyndham Beaver FallsRiver VueMarket Square PlacePiatt PlaceHilton Garden Inn Pittsburgh - SouthpointeJacksons Restaurant + BarSouthpointeCrossroads CenterSt. Clair Hospital Outpatient CenterHighmark Stadium
CategoriesMixed-UseDevelopmentHospitalityHotelRestaurantCommercialResidentialEntertainmentMedicalInterior DesignPittsburghWashingtonCanonsburgBeaverWestmoreland
NewsNewslettersPress ReleasesNewsContactMedia
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
IP ADDRESSES
Millcraft Investments records IP (Internet Protocol) address numbers and other site usage statistics to better understand how visitors use our website.
COOKIES
“Cookies” are small text files that a website transfers to a site visitor’s hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking website usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information like a person’s name or e-mail address. To measure the effectiveness of our online presence, Millcraft Investments uses cookies to identify repeat visitors to our website, to determine the path visitors take on our site, and to identify unique visitors. Any information gathered using cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis.
REGISTRATION FORMS
Personal information gathered from registration forms (such as name, email or street address) is used to send information related to our products and services to consenting users. When you indicate that you want to receive a product or service, or contact a person or organization, we share the data needed for you to receive what you have indicated. You may be contacted for future promotions, services, or announcements. You are welcome to unsubscribe or change your preferences anytime by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the email, or contact us directly at info@millcraftideas.com to be removed from our communications. We apologize for any inconvenience.
SECURITY
Although we will make every effort to protect personal information, no computer system is immune from hackers and others who might misuse information. We are not responsible for any breach of security that is beyond our reasonable control.
LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES
This website contains hyperlinks to websites operated by parties other than Millcraft Investments. Please be aware that these sites may record personal information and other data according to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to review any privacy policies or notices posted on those linked sites. Millcraft Investments does not explicitly support or condone all content by other parties.
HYPERLINKS
This website contains hyperlinks or “links” to other sites, and other sites may “link” to this site. Websites linking to and from this site may have different privacy practices and policies than the ones described here for www.millcraftideas.com. Visitors to our site should read the terms of use and privacy statements of other websites they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
CHANGES TO MILLCRAFT INVESTMENTS’ POLICY
Millcraft Investments may, from time to time, make changes to this policy. We recommend that visitors to this site re-visit this privacy policy on occasion to learn of new privacy practices and changes to our policy.
HOW TO GET IN TOUCH WITH US ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY
It’s important to us at Millcraft Investments to hear what visitors have to say about our services and our policies. If site visitors have any questions, concerns, or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or want to let us know what they think about any of our off-line and online products and services, they can email us at info@millcraftideas.com.
– Disclaimer –
Millcraft Investments, Millcraft Real Estate Services LLC, and Piatt Sotheby’s International Realty fully supports the principles of the Fair Housing Act and the Equal Opportunity Act. Each Office Is Independently Owned and Operated. Although information has been obtained by sources deemed reliable, Owner, Millcraft Investments, Millcraft Real Estate Services LLC, and/or its representatives, brokers, or agents make no guarantee as to the accuracy of the information contained herein, and offer the Property without express or implied warranties of any kind. The offer related to the Property may be withdrawn or changed without notice.
Millcraft Real Estate Services, LLC | #RB066678 | Broker Mark Jennings | 380 Southpointe Boulevard, Suite 400, Canonsburg PA 15317 | 724-222-1004 | Fax 724-884-0474
SEARCH
Privacy Policy
Southpointe 380 Southpointe Boulevard
Suite 400
Canonsburg, PA 15317
724-229-8800
Pittsburgh 260 Forbes Avenue
Suite 1550
Pittsburgh PA 15222
412-471-1604
In an effort to support our Millcraft Hospitality employees impacted by COVID-19 we ask you to consider donating https://t.co/P1qHybif3Q170 days agoTONIGHT! Show your #lovefrompgh - head outside at 8PM, turn on your lights, and give an illumination ovation to tho… https://t.co/BJrnRg2DdG185 days agoA statement from the leadership team at Millcraft about how we are conducting business in response to the spread of… https://t.co/9Aywuci4TC200 days ago
Read more tweets from Millcraft
Copyright © 2019 Millcraft Investments.
Top
